dexplatform.com 2012-12-15

# DexPlatform.com Publishers Network

Privacy policy

THE DexPlatform.com PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES.

This privacy policy ("Policy") describes DexPlatform.com Network's ("APO") provision of a technology and advertising platform for marketers and content publishers such as web sites or email newsletters and operators (together, referred to as "Publishers" or "Publisher Properties") to attempt to deliver more relevant advertisements to consumers. DexPlatform.com does not collect, obtain or maintain personally identifiable information ("PII") from Publishers who use our PPAd technology product. The data collected and maintained by DexPlatform.com from Publishers using PPAd™ technology ("Anonymous Information") is not sufficient to permit someone to identify a particular consumer by name, email address, mailing address, telephone number or through social security number, driver's license or other government issued ID. This Policy does not apply to the practices of Publishers or other companies that DexPlatform.com does not own or control or to people that DexPlatform.com does not employ or manage. DexPlatform.com retains its rights to enter into new or different lines of business with consumers and if and to the extent it does so, it may display a different Privacy Policy to the consumer for such lines of business.

DexPlatform.com Collection of Information.

**1.1** User Information. DexPlatform.com does not track or maintain PII about consumers. It maintains Anonymous Information including behavior data (i.e., visiting a particular website or clicking on a particular ad) and demographic or similar data (i.e., browser type or lifestyle data). DexPlatform.com may maintain PII information if it is in an encrypted format which cannot be decrypted; that is, the data as stored is Anonymous Information rather than PII. For example, a Publisher may encrypt the email address joe@smith.com into the term "123abc" with a one-way encryption routine and transfer the term "123abc" to DexPlatform.com to store on DexPlatform.com's computers, but it is not currently feasible for DexPlatform.com or others, due to the sophistication of the encryption routines utilized, to decode the term "123abc" back into the original email address, joe@smith.com.

**1.2** User Behaviors Collected with Cookies, and Other Information. DexPlatform.com may use cookies and IP addresses to associate your Anonymous Information (as described in Section 1.1 above) with an anonymous profile containing data such as your online behaviors, which could include records on viewing, opening or clicking on a particular online advertisement or visiting a website operated by a Publisher. Additionally, DexPlatform.com may use other new and evolving sources of information and information gathering in the future (together, "Technology Information") to assist Publishers in delivering more relevant advertisements to you.  
Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows DexPlatform.com to identify your IP address with corresponding information in DexPlatform.com's database. DexPlatform.com may use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements when an advertisement has been viewed on Publisher Properties. You may read more about cookies at http://www.cookiecentral.com/.  
IP Addresses. DexPlatform.com may use your IP address to better target an ad to you or people in your area. Unless you use a static IP address, an IP address relates to households or larger communities. For example, if you use a national Internet Service Provider (ISP) to access the Internet, such as America Online, it may not be possible to determine your geographic location based on your IP address. If you use a local ISP, it may be possible to narrow your community to a fewer number of people or businesses which your ISP services. Because an individual does not own a particular IP address, a consumer's IP address is not personally identifiable information and may change for any number of reasons over time, e.g., even if you rent a static IP address for a limited period.  
Where Technology Information is Collected. Technology Information is collected directly from DexPlatform.com advertisements or indirectly through Publishers that DexPlatform.com contracts with to display advertisements. Such advertisements will usually be displayed within one of the following advertising vehicles:  
Websites. DexPlatform.com may set a cookie on your computer or associate behavior with your Internet service provider's IP address when you view advertisements delivered on Publisher websites. After a behavior is associated to a cookie or an IP address, DexPlatform.com may track how you interact with the advertisement and the Publisher website (for example, registering, purchasing, browsing, etc.).  
Email. DexPlatform.com may track your interaction with emails sent to you on behalf of Publishers (for example, when you open or click on an email, register, purchase, or browse in response to such email), but does not maintain a list of email addresses or other PII in connection with this activity.

**1.3** Outside Information. DexPlatform.com may lawfully receive information about you, including demographic data, purchasing trends and similar information, from third parties, such as information located in public databases ("Outside Information"). Outside Information shall be Anonymous Information.

**1.4** No Information Collected from Minors. MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 18 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO DexPlatform.com. If DexPlatform.com is notified it has any information about a minor under the age of 18, that information will be promptly deleted from our active database.  
Use of Information and User Data.

**2.1** Discretion to Use Information. DexPlatform.com may share Anonymous Information about your behaviors with trusted Publishers under confidentiality agreements. These Publishers may use this information to better target advertisements to you. If you wish to end your email subscription with a Publisher, you may follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe or follow the instructions detailed at Section 4 below.

**2.2** Targeted Advertising Delivered by Publishers. DexPlatform.com uses Anonymous Information to assist its Publishes in targeting advertisements more effectively. When a consumer is online, DexPlatform.com uses Technology Information to associate an individual with their Anonymous Information and DexPlatform.com assists its Publishers in attempting to show information and advertising for products and services to which the consumer may respond. DexPlatform.com may use data collected from a response to one type of advertising or information for targeting advertisements or other information through a different venue. For example, DexPlatform.com may inform an email Publisher that a consumer responded to a baseball banner advertisement and that Publisher may try to deliver to the consumer a baseball-related advertisement and other information to the consumer via email.

**2.3** Legal Process. DexPlatform.com may disclose information in its possession and control to respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required by law.

**2.4** Summary Data. DexPlatform.com may sell or transfer Anonymous Information, such as summary or aggregated non-PII about consumers or consumer sub-groups.

**2.5** Storage and Protection of Information. DexPlatform.com stores Anonymous Information in a database on DexPlatform.com computers. These computers have security measures, such as a firewall, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under DexPlatform.com's control. DexPlatform.com also maintains physical and procedural safeguards to protect information. Furthermore, DexPlatform.com maintains the data in its database in encrypted form, so that even if the data is improperly accessed, it is less likely to be in a format intelligible or useable for purposes not authorized or intended by DexPlatform.com. Notwithstanding such measures, DexPlatform.com cannot guarantee that its security or privacy protection measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed and the data on them stolen or altered.

Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

**3.1** Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Publishers who place advertisements on the Internet may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about you. DexPlatform.com does not control Publishers' use of such technology.

**3.2** Links. The Publishers' Websites and email messages transmitted on behalf of Publishers may contain hypertext links to the Websites of third parties. DexPlatform.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

**3.3** Publishers. To learn about how a particular Publisher may use your PII or Anonymous Information, you should read the privacy policy of that Publisher.

How You May Exercise Your Privacy Rights And Unsubscribe.  
  
Websites. To prevent the display of Publisher or DexPlatform.com advertising on a Website, for example, banner advertisements, do not visit the Website. To only prevent DexPlatform.com from tracking your behavior on a Website, turn off cookies, utilize a changing IP address, and do not click on or interact with any advertisements.

Email Databases. To unsubscribe from Publisher email lists, click the link included in the footer of any message you receive from the Publisher.

Please read the privacy policy of particular Publishers to understand how your PII and Anonymous Information may be used after you unsubscribe.

More Information.

DexPlatform.com reserves the right to update this Policy at any time by re-publishing it to this Website with a new effective date. The current policy has an effective as of December 20, 2010 (v1.0.22). If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at support [at] DexPlatform.com
